{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Data and Digital Communications",
    "Term": "Midterms",
    "Title": "Quiz Reviewer for Midterms",
    "LastModified": "20 October 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "3_Handout_1 & 04_Handout_1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "This media type does not require physical links between two or more devices",
      "answer": "Unguided Media",
      "choices": [
        "Unguided Media",
        "Guided Media",
        "Microwaves",
        "Infrared"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following best describes latency?",
      "answer": "It is a measure of delay",
      "choices": [
        "It is a measure of delay",
        "It is the amount of data that can be transmitted per second",
        "It is the amount of data that enters and goes through a system",
        "It is used when data is transmitted as individual characters"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following best describes a lightning interface?",
      "answer": "It is an 8-pin connector in which it can be found as the primary connector on the newer versions of Apple's iPhone",
      "choices": [
        "It is an 8-pin connector in which it can be found as the primary connector on the newer versions of Apple's iPhone",
        "It supports data transfer rates up to billions of bits per second",
        "It is a digital interface that uses a standardized connector (plug) for all serial and parallel type devices",
        "It is a type of interconnection between peripheral devices and a microcomputer"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which best describes the Fire Wire interface?",
      "answer": "It is a type of interconnection between peripheral devices and a microcomputer",
      "choices": [
        "It is a type of interconnection between peripheral devices and a microcomputer",
        "It is an 8-pin connector in which it can be found as the primary connector on the newer versions of Apple's iPhone",
        "It supports data transfer rates up to billions of bits per second",
        "It is a digital interface that uses a standardized connector (plug) for all serial and parallel type devices"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which best describes the Fire Wire interface?",
      "answer": "It is capable of supporting transfer speeds of up to 3.2 Gbps",
      "choices": [
        "It is capable of supporting transfer speeds of up to 3.2 Gbps",
        "It is an 8-pin connector in which it can be found as the primary connector on the newer versions of Apple's iPhone",
        "It supports data transfer rates up to billions of bits per second",
        "It is a digital interface that uses a standardized connector (plug) for all serial and parallel type devices"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following best describes throughput?",
      "answer": "It is the amount of data that enters and goes through a system",
      "choices": [
        "It is the amount of data that enters and goes through a system",
        "It is a measure of delay",
        "It is the amount of data that can be transmitted per second",
        "It is used when data is transmitted as individual characters"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements best describes a full-duplex transmission?",
      "answer": "Data can flow in both directions simultaneously.",
      "choices": [
        "Data can flow in both directions simultaneously.",
        "Data can only flow in one direction",
        "Data can flow in both directions, but never simultaneously",
        "Data can flow in any direction"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It refers to the leakage of signal from the medium due to undesirable electrical characteristics.",
      "answer": "Radiation",
      "choices": [
        "Radiation",
        "Bandwidth",
        "Noise Absorption",
        "Attentuation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This data transmission is used to transmit large blocks of data at a time",
      "answer": "Synchronous",
      "choices": [
        "Synchronous",
        "Asynchronous",
        "Isochronous",
        "Anonymous"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following best describes a mechanical component?",
      "answer": "It deals with item such as the connector or plugs description.",
      "choices": [
        "It deals with item such as the connector or plugs description.",
        "It deals with the function of each pin used in an interface",
        "It deals with voltages, line capacitance, and other electrical issues.",
        "It describes how the circuits are used to perform an operation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following best describes a sky wave?",
      "answer": "This is used for the propagation of EM waves with a frequency range of 3-30 Mhz",
      "choices": [
        "This is used for the propagation of EM waves with a frequency range of 3-30 Mhz",
        "This is used for Line of sight comunication",
        "This type of progation employs the use of large antennas order of which is equivalent to the wavelength of the waves",
        "Space satellite communication and very highfrequency waves use this propagation method"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following best describes a sky wave?",
      "answer": "These waves makes the use of ionosphere in which it is the ionized part of the earth’s upper atmosphere",
      "choices": [
        "These waves makes the use of ionosphere in which it is the ionized part of the earth’s upper atmosphere",
        "This is used for Line of sight comunication",
        "This type of progation employs the use of large antennas order of which is equivalent to the wavelength of the waves",
        "Space satellite communication and very highfrequency waves use this propagation method"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following implies collision avoidance?",
      "answer": "The switch tries to prevent collision by having the intention of each computer to transmit signal before transmission",
      "choices": [
        "The switch tries to prevent collision by having the intention of each computer to transmit signal before transmission",
        "Collisions are eliminated under token passing because only a computer that possesses a free token can transmit.",
        "An active hub is an essential requirement that can control access to the network",
        "The terminals on a network are required to obtain permission from the hub before they start transmitting the bytes over a network"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements best describes half-duplex transmission?",
      "answer": "Data can flow in both direction, but never simultaneously",
      "choices": [
        "Data can flow in both direction, but never simultaneously",
        "Data can flow in both directions simultaneously.",
        "Data can only flow in one direction",
        "Data can flow in any direction"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It refers to the susceptibility of the media to external electrical noise that causes distortion.",
      "answer": "Noise Absorption",
      "choices": [
        "Noise Absorption",
        "Attenuation",
        "Bandwidth",
        "Radiation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is currently found on Apple laptops and provides a 10-Gbps connection.",
      "answer": "Thunderbolt",
      "choices": [
        "Thunderbolt",
        "Fire Wire",
        "USB",
        "InfiniBand"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This dataflow transmission can only flow in one direction",
      "answer": "Simplex",
      "choices": [
        "Simplex",
        "Duplex",
        "Half-Duplex",
        "Triplex"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In CSMA/CD, it means that when a collision is detected, the stations stop transmitting and wait a random length of time before retransmitting.",
      "answer": "Collision Detection",
      "choices": [
        "Collision Detection",
        "Carrier Sense",
        "Multiple Access",
        "Token Passing"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements best describes a ground wave?",
      "answer": "This type of progation employs the use of large antennas order of which is equivalent to the wavelength of the waves",
      "choices": [
        "This type of progation employs the use of large antennas order of which is equivalent to the wavelength of the waves",
        "This is used for the propagation of EM waves with a frequency range of 3-30 Mhz",
        "These waves makes the use of ionosphere in which it is the ionized part of the earth’s upper atmosphere",
        "This is used for Line of sight comunication"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is TRUE  about asynchronous transmission?",
      "answer": "It is used when data is transmitted as individual characters",
      "choices": [
        "It is used when data is transmitted as individual characters",
        "It is used to transmit large blocks of data at a time",
        "Data is usually organized in frames and each frame is preceded by a flag that consists of a few bits and terminated by another flag",
        "Multiple data bits are transmitted over multiple channels at the same time"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements best describes space waves?",
      "answer": "This is used for Line of sight comunication",
      "choices": [
        "This is used for Line of sight comunication",
        "This type of progation employs the use of large antennas order of which is equivalent to the wavelength of the waves",
        "This is used for the propagation of EM waves with a frequency range of 3-30 Mhz",
        "These waves makes the use of ionosphere in which it is the ionized part of the earth’s upper atmosphere"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a digital interface that uses a standardized connector for serial and parallel devices, known for being hot pluggable",
      "answer": "Universal Serial Bus",
      "choices": [
        "Universal Serial Bus",
        "Lighting",
        "Fire Wire",
        "SCSI - SCSI"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a way of sending multiple signals or streams of information over a communication link at the same time as a single signal",
      "answer": "Multiplexing",
      "choices": [
        "Multiplexing",
        "Demultiplexing",
        "Simplexing",
        "Wave Propagation"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is a serial that connects a computer to multiple input/output devices that supports data transfer rates IP to billions of bit per second, but it can support the interconnection of up to 126 devices only",
      "answer": "Fibre Channel",
      "choices": [
        "Fibre Channel",
        "Lighting",
        "Infiband",
        "Thunderbold"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following implies multiple access?",
      "answer": "Many computers are attempting to transmit and compete for the opportunity to send data",
      "choices": [
        "Many computers are attempting to transmit and compete for the opportunity to send data",
        "It means that each station on the LAN continually listens to the cable for the presence of a signal before transmitting",
        "It means that when a collision is detected, the stations will stop transmitting",
        "Instead of detecting and reacting to collisions, CSMA/CA tries to avoid them"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It enables the transfer of information between two or more points that are connected by an electrical conductor",
      "answer": "Guided Media",
      "choices": [
        "Guided Media",
        "Unguided Media",
        "Multi Media",
        "Radio Waves"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This type of antenna is made of a series of dipoles placed along it axis at different space interval of time followed by a logarithmic function of frequency",
      "answer": "Log Periodic Antennas",
      "choices": [
        "Log Periodic Antennas",
        "Wire Antennas",
        "Microwave Antennas",
        "Traveling Wave Antennas"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "This kind of unguided media is used for very short distance communication in which it cannot penetrate through obstacles.",
      "answer": "Infrared",
      "choices": [
        "Infrared",
        "Microwave",
        "Radio waves",
        "Bluetooth"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements is TRUE  about Synchronous transmission?",
      "answer": "It is used to transmit large blocks of data at a time",
      "choices": [
        "It is used to transmit large blocks of data at a time",
        "It is used when data is transmitted as individual characters",
        "Multiple data bits are transmitted over multiple channels at the same time",
        "Each character is preceded by one start bit and one or two stop bits that are used by the receiver"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is considered a standard for a given application although it has no official status",
      "answer": "De Facto Standard",
      "choices": [
        "De Facto Standard",
        "De Factor Standard",
        "Facto De Standard",
        "Em Facto Standard"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following statements best describes Time-division multiplexing?",
      "answer": "It is divided into non-overlapping time slots that are assigned to users in which transmissions are staggered using a round-robin method to schedule the transmission",
      "choices": [
        "It is divided into non-overlapping time slots that are assigned to users in which transmissions are staggered using a round-robin method to schedule the transmission",
        "It is partitioned into multiple frequency blocks called channels that are assigned to users",
        "It is where the output signal, which appears like noise, occupies more bandwidth than the original signal",
        "It means that each station on the LAN continually listens to the cable for the presence of a signal before transmitting"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "In CSMA/CD, it means many computers attempt to transmit and compete for the opportunity to send data",
      "answer": "Multiple Access",
      "choices": [
        "Multiple Access",
        "Carrier Sense",
        "Collision Detection",
        "Demand Priority"
      ],
      "reference": "Quiz_Reviewer",
      "term": "Midterms"
    }
  ]
}